# CHRISTIAN RUIZ

### DEVELOPER





+57 310-867-2765



christianjavieruizcortes@gmail.com



mugen-portfolio.vercel.app

## **PROFILE**

Front-end web developer with almost 3 years of experience, passionate and dedicated to staying up to date with the latest trends and tools in technology. I am confident in my ability to contribute positively to any development team.

# SKILLS

- Html
- Css: Sass, Bem, Itcss, Bootstrap, **Tailwind**
- Javascript
- React js: Hooks, Context, Redux
- Next is
- · Node js: Express
- Nest is
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Scrum
- Tools: VS Code, GIT, Figma
- Web Design

# EXPERIENCE

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Educamás

2021 - 2022

- Design and development of various web aplications
- web application maintenance
- web application optimization

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Freelance

2020 - Present

· Development of different web applications focused mainly on the frontend

# EDUCATION

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

Programate

2022 - 2023

### **SELF-TAUGHT**

Internet research

2020 - Present

## LANGUAJES

SPANISH: NATIVE

**ENGLISH: CERTIFIED C1** 

#### **PRODUCT OWNER**

Educamás

2022 - 2022

- Make product and roadmap decisions based on business and user needs.
- Work with the development team to ensure delivery of value to the customer.
- interact with the customer and transform their needs into requirements for the product

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Shark Technology

2023 - 2023

- Web desing
- Development of various web aplications
- · web application optimization